Finding Aid for William G. Milliken papers 1961-1982
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence
  - Chronological 1969-1982, 554 linear feet
    - 1976
      - General Subjects 1976
        - A (Box 274)
        - A-D (Box 275)
        - D-G (Box 276)
        - G-L (Box 277)
        - L (Box 278)
        - L-P (Box 279)
        - P (Box 280)
        - P-R (Box 281)
        - R-T (Box 282)
        - T (Box 283)
        - U-Z (Box 284)
        - Miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 284)
        - Habitual Letter Writers, 9 folders (Box 285)
      - Departments and Commissions 1976
        - Management and Budget (formerly Administration)
          - Director's File (Gerald H. Miller) (Box 285)
          - General
            - A-J, 10 folders (Box 286)
            - K-Z, 12 folders (Box 287)
          - Aging Commission (Box 288)
            - A-Z, 3 folders (Box 288)
            - Copy file (Box 288)
            - Material file (Box 288)
          - Bicentennial
            - A-Z, 7 folders (Box 288)
            - Copy file (Box 289)
          - Criminal Justice
            - A-Z, 3 folders (Box 289)
            - Copy file (Box 289)
          - Health and Medical Affairs
            - A-Z, 4 folders (Box 289)
            - Copy file (Box 289)
          - Nutrition
            - A-Z (Box 289)
            - Copy file (Box 289)
          - Retirement
            - A-S, 4 folders (Box 289)
            - T-Z (Box 290)
          - Veterans' Trust Fund
            - A-Z, 2 folders (Box 290)
            - Copy file (Box 290)
        - Agriculture
          - Director's File (B. Dale Ball) (Box 290)
          - General, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 290)
          - Copy file (Box 290)
          - Material file (Box 290)
        - Attorney General
          - Frank J. Kelley (Box 290)
          - General, A-Z (Box 290)
          - Copy file (Box 290)
        - Civil Rights
          - Director's File (Ruth Rasmussen) (Box 290)
          - General, A-Z, 3 folders (Box 290)
          - Copy file (Box 290)
        - Civil Service
          - General, A-Z, 3 folders (Box 291)
          - Copy file (Box 291)
        - Commerce
          - Director's File (Richard K. Helmbrecht) (Box 291)
          - General, A-Z, 2 folders (Box 291)
          - Economic Expansion
            - A-L (Box 291)
            - M-Z (Box 292)
            - Copy file (Box 292)
          - Energy
            - A-Z, 4 folders (Box 292)
            - Copy file (Box 292)
          - Insurance Commission
            - A-R (Box 292)
            - S-Z (Box 293)
            - Copy file (Box 293)
          - Liquor Control Commission
            - A-Z, 2 folders (Box 293)
            - Copy file (Box 293)
          - Public Service Commission
            - A-Z, 8 folders (Box 293)
            - Copy file (Box 293)
          - Tourist Council (Box 294)
        - Corrections
          - Director's File (Perry M. Johnson) (Box 294)
          - Copy file (Box 294)
          - Material File (Box 294)
          - Inmates
            - A-K, 10 folders (Box 294)
            - L-Wi, 10 folders (Box 295)
            - Wo-Z (Box 296)
            - Copy file (Box 296)
          - Pardons and Paroles, A-Z, 3 folders (Box 296)
        - Education
          - Superintendent's File (John W. Porter) (Box 296)
          - General
            - A-H, 8 folders (Box 296)
            - I-V, 10 folders (Box 297)
            - W-Z, 2 folders (Box 298)
          - Copy file (S.B. 484), 2 folders (Box 298)
        - Highways
          - Director's File (John P. Woodford) (Box 298)
          - General
            - A-V (Box 298)
            - W-Z (Box 299)
          - Copy file (Box 299)
        - Labor
          - Director's File (Keith Molin) (Box 299)
          - General
            - A-R, 7 folders (Box 299)
            - S-Z, 3 folders (Box 300)
          - Copy file (Box 300)
          - Juvenile Justice Services
            - Director's File (Box 300)
            - A-Z (Box 300)
            - Copy file (Box 300)
          - Michigan Employment Securities Commission
            - Director's File (S. Martin Taylor) (Box 300)
            - A-Z, 8 folders (Box 300)
          - Michigan Equal Opportunity Office (Grant file) (Box 301)
        - Licensing and Regulation
          - Director's File (Beverly J. Clark) (Box 301)
          - General, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 301)
          - Copy file (Box 301)
        - Lottery, State
          - General, A-Z, 2 folders (Box 301)
          - Copy file (Box 301)
        - Mental Health
          - Director's File (Donald C. Smith) (Box 301)
          - General
            - A-M, 5 folders (Box 301)
            - N-Z, 3 folders (Box 302)
          - Copy file (Box 302)
        - Military Affairs
          - General, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 302)
          - Copy file (Box 302)
        - Natural Resources
          - Director's File (Howard A. Tanner) (Box 302)
          - General
            - A-G (Box 302)
            - H-T (Box 303)
            - U-Z (Box 304)
          - Copy file (Box 304)
          - Material file (Box 304)
        - Police, State
          - Director's File (George L. Halverson), 2 folders (Box 304)
          - General, A-Z, 7 folders (Box 304)
          - Copy file (Box 304)
          - Material file (Box 304)
          - Highway Safety Board (copy file) (Box 304)
        - Public Health
          - Director's File (Maurice S. Reizen) (Box 304)
          - General
            - A-C, 3 folders (Box 304)
            - D-Z, 10 folders (Box 305)
          - Copy file (Box 305)
        - Social Services
          - Director's File (John T. Dempsey) (Box 306)
          - General
            - A-P, 11 folders (Box 306)
            - R-Z, 5 folders (Box 307)
          - Copy file (Box 307)
          - Housing Authority
            - A-Z (Box 307)
            - Copy file (Box 307)
          - Human Services Network (copy file) (Box 307)
          - Medicaid
            - A-R, 6 folders (Box 307)
            - S-Z, 2 folders (Box 308)
            - Copy file (Box 308)
          - Social Services Division
            - A-H, 8 folders (Box 308)
            - I-V, 11 folders (Box 309)
            - W-Z, 2 folders (Box 310)
            - Copy file (Box 310)
        - State, Secretary of
          - Richard A. Austin File (Box 310)
          - General, A-Z, 5 folders (Box 310)
          - Copy file (Box 310)
          - Michigan Historical Commission (Box 310)
        - Supreme Court
          - General, A-Z (Box 310)
          - Copy file (Box 310)
        - Treasury
          - Allison Green (Box 310)
          - General
            - A-G, 2 folders (Box 310)
            - H-Z, 5 folders (Box 311)
          - Copy file (Box 311)
        - Urban Affairs (Box 311)
        - Volunteers in Michigan (Box 311)
      - Federal Subjects, 1976
        - A-E (Box 311)
        - E-N (Box 312)
        - P-Z (Box 313)
      - Legislative 1976
        - General
          - A-Mc, 7 folders (Box 313)
          - Ma-Z, 7 folders (Box 314)
        - Copy file (Box 314)
    - 1977 (Box 315)
      - General Subjects. 1977
        - A-D (Box 315)
        - D-L (Box 316)
        - L (Box 317)
        - L-M (Box 318)
        - N-P (Box 319)
        - P (Box 320)
        - P-R (Box 321)
        - R-T (Box 322)
        - T-V (Box 323)
        - V-Z (Box 324)
        - Miscellaneous
          - A-R, 14 folders (Box 324)
          - S-Z, 2 folders (Box 325)
        - Habitual Letter Writers, A-Z, 15 folders (Box 325)
      - Departments and Commissions 1977
        - Management and Budget (formerly Administration)
          - Director's File (Gerald H. Miller) (Box 326)
          - General
            - A-M, 1 folders (Box 326)
            - N-Z, 8 folders (Box 327)
          - Copy file (Box 327)
          - Aging Commission
            - A-S (Box 327)
            - T-Z (Box 328)
            - Copy/Material file (Box 328)
          - Bicentennial (Box 328)
          - Crime Victims (Box 328)
          - Criminal Justice (Box 328)
          - Efficiency (Box 328)
          - Health and Medical Affairs, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 328)
          - Juvenile Justice (Box 328)
          - Nutrition (Box 328)
          - State Employees Retirement System (Box 328)
          - Veteran Affairs (Box 328)
        - Agriculture
          - Director's File (B. Dale Ball) (Box 328)
          - General
            - A-Do, 2 folders (Box 328)
            - Dr-Z, 7 folders (Box 329)
          - Copy file (Box 329)
        - Attorney General
          - Frank J. Kelley (Box 329)
          - General, A-Z, 2 folders (Box 329)
        - Auditor General (Box 329)
        - Civil Rights
          - Director's File (Ruth Rasmussen) (Box 329)
          - General, A-Z, 9 folders (Box 329)
        - Civil Service
          - General, A-Z, 5 folders (Box 330)
          - Copy file (Box 330)
        - Commerce
          - Director's File (Richard K. Helmbrecht) (Box 330)
          - General
            - A-Sc, 6 folders (Box 330)
            - Se-Z (Box 331)
          - Economic Expansion
            - A-Z, 6 folders (Box 331)
            - Material file (Box 331)
          - Energy
            - A-Ma, 5 folders (Box 331)
            - Me-Z, 3 folders (Box 332)
          - Insurance Commission
            - A-T (Box 332)
            - V-Z (Box 333)
          - Liquor Control Commission
            - A-Z, 3 folders (Box 333)
            - Material file (Box 333)
          - Public Service Commission
            - A-Re, 8 folders (Box 333)
            - Ri-Z, 3 folders (Box 334)
          - Tourist Council (Box 334)
        - Corrections
          - Director's File (Perry M. Johnson) (Box 334)
          - Inmates
            - A-El, 2 folders (Box 334)
            - Em-Pz, 10 folders (Box 335)
            - Q-Z, 6 folders (Box 336)
          - Pardons and Paroles
            - A-G, 4 folders (Box 336)
            - H-Z, 7 folders (Box 337)
        - Education
          - Superintendent's File (John W. Porter) (Box 337)
          - General
            - A-Ca, 2 folders (Box 337)
            - Ch-S, 10 folders (Box 338)
            - T-Z, 2 folders (Box 339)
          - Copy file (Box 339)
        - Highways
          - Director's File (John P. Woodford) (Box 339)
          - General
            - A-F, 5 folders (Box 339)
            - G-Z, 10 folders (Box 340)
        - Labor
          - Director's File (Keith Molin) (Box 341)
          - General
            - A-O, 9 folders (Box 341)
            - P-Z, 5 folders (Box 342)
          - Grants, 2 folders (Box 342)
          - Michigan Employment Securities Commission
            - A-L, 4 folders (Box 342)
            - M-Z, 4 folders (Box 343)
            - Copy file (Box 343)
        - Licensing and Regulations
          - Director's File (Beverly J. Clark) (Box 343)
          - General, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 343)
        - Lottery, State
          - Commissioner's File (Gus Harrison) (Box 343)
          - A-Z (Box 343)
        - Mental Health
          - Director's File (Donald C. Smith) (Box 343)
          - General, A-Z, 6 folders (Box 344)
        - Military Affairs
          - John A. Johnston (Box 344)
          - General, A-Z (Box 344)
          - Copy/Material file (Box 344)
        - Natural Resources
          - Director's File (Howard A. Tanner) (Box 345)
          - General
            - A-K, 9 folders (Box 347)
            - L-Z, 10 folders (Box 346)
        - Police, State
          - Director's File (Gerald L. Hough) (Box 346)
          - General, A-Z, 8 folders (Box 346)
          - Copy file (Box 346)
        - Public Health
          - Director's File (Maurice S. Reizen) (Box 346)
          - General
            - A-C, 2 folders (Box 346)
            - D-Z, 8 folders (Box 348)
        - Social Services
          - Director's File (John T. Dempsey) (Box 348)
          - General
            - A-J, 2 folders (Box 348)
            - K-Z, 3 folders (Box 349)
          - Housing Authority, A-Z (Box 349)
          - Medicaid, A-Z, 5 folders (Box 349)
          - Social Services Division
            - A-Blu, 3 folders (Box 349)
            - Bm-Her, 11 folders (Box 350)
            - Hig-Pa, 11 folders (Box 351)
            - Pe-Wik, 12 folders (Box 352)
            - Win-Z, 2 folders (Box 353)
        - State, Secretary of
          - General, A-Z, 6 folders (Box 353)
          - Copy/Material file (Box 353)
          - Michigan Historical Division (Box 353)
        - Treasury
          - General
            - A-E, 4 folders (Box 353)
            - F-Z, 11 folders (Box 354)
          - Copy file (Box 354)
        - Urban Affairs (Box 354)
        - Volunteers in Michigan (Box 354)
      - Federal Subjects 1977
        - A-H (Box 355)
        - H [I-Z in box 1538] (Box 356)
        - I-Z (Box 1538)
      - Legislative 1977
        - General (Box 356)
          - A-P, 9 folders (Box 356)
          - R-Z, 4 folders (Box 357)
        - Copy file (Box 357)
    - 1978
      - General Subjects 1978
        - A-D (Box 357)
        - D-L (Box 358)
        - L (Box 359)
        - L-P (Box 360)
        - P (Box 361)
        - P (Box 362)
        - P-R (Box 363)
        - R-T (Box 364)
        - T (Box 365)
        - T-Z (Box 366)
        - Miscellaneous, A-Z, 5 folders (Box 366)
        - Habitual Letter Writers
          - A-C (Box 366)
          - D-Z, 7 folders (Box 367)
      - Departments and Commissions 1978
        - Management and Budget
          - Director's File (Gerald H. Miller) (Box 368)
          - General
            - A-M, 12 folders (Box 368)
            - N-Z, 7 folders (Box 369)
          - Copy file (Box 369)
          - Aging Commission, A-Z, 2 folders (Box 369)
          - Crime Victims (Box 369)
          - Criminal Justice, 2 folders (Box 370)
          - Health and Medical Affairs (Box 370)
          - Retirement (Box 370)
          - Veterans' Trust Fund (Box 370)
        - Agriculture
          - Director's File (B. Dale Ball) (Box 370)
          - General
            - A-S, 11 folders (Box 370)
            - T-Z, 2 folders (Box 371)
          - PBB (student letters/sampled) (Box 371)
        - Attorney General
          - Frank J. Kelley (Box 371)
          - General, A-Z (Box 371)
        - Auditor General (Albert Lee file) (Box 371)
        - Civil Rights Commission
          - Director's File (Ruth Rasmussen) (Box 371)
          - General, A-Z, 2 folders (Box 371)
        - Civil Service
          - Director's File (Richard A. Ross) (Box 371)
          - General, A-Z, 8 folders (Box 371)
        - Commerce
          - Director's File (Richard K. Helmbrecht) (Box 372)
          - General, A-Z, 8 folders (Box 372)
          - Economic Expansion
            - A-L, 5 folders (Box 372)
            - M-Z, 4 folders (Box 373)
          - Energy Crisis, A-Z, 8 folders (Box 373)
          - Insurance Commission, A-Z, 9 folders (Box 374)
          - Liquor Control Commission, A-Z, 3 folders (Box 374)
          - Public Service Commission
            - A-B (Box 374)
            - C-Z (Box 375)
        - Corrections
          - Director's File (Perry M. Johnson) (Box 375)
          - General
            - A-D (Box 375)
            - E-Z (Box 376)
          - Inmates
            - A-H, 7 folders (Box 376)
            - I-V, 8 folders (Box 377)
            - W-Z, 2 folders (Box 378)
        - Education
          - Superintendent's File (John W. Porter) (Box 378)
          - General
            - A-F, 3 folders (Box 378)
            - G-S, 6 folders (Box 379)
            - T-Z, 2 folders (Box 380)
        - Highways
          - Director's File (John P. Woodford) (Box 380)
          - General
            - A-F, 4 folders (Box 380)
            - G-Z, 9 folders (Box 381)
        - Labor (Box 382)
          - Director's File (C. Patrick Babcock) (Box 382)
          - General
            - A-M, 8 folders (Box 382)
            - N-Z, 2 folders (Box 383)
          - Michigan Equal Opportunity Office
            - Grant (Box 383)
            - A-Z, 3 folders (Box 383)
        - Licensing and Regulations
          - Director's File (William S. Ballenger, III) (Box 384)
          - General, A-Z (Box 384)
        - Lottery, State (Box 384)
        - Mental Health
          - Director's File (Donald C. Smith) (Box 384)
          - General
            - A-C (Box 384)
            - D-Z (Box 385)
        - Military Affairs (Johnston/General A-Z/Material) (Box 385)
        - Natural Resources
          - Director's File (Howard A. Tanner) (Box 385)
          - General
            - A-K, 8 folders (Box 386)
            - L-Z, 9 folders (Box 387)
        - Police, State
          - Director's File (Gerald L. Hough) (Box 388)
          - General, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 388)
        - Public Health
          - Director's File (Maurice S. Reizen) (Box 388)
          - General
            - A-D, 3 folders (Box 388)
            - E-Z, 8 folders (Box 389)
          - Nutrition (Box 389)
        - Social Services
          - Director's File (John T. Dempsey) (Box 389)
          - General
            - A (Box 389)
            - B-G, 9 folders (Box 390)
            - G-M, 7 folders (Box 391)
            - M-S, 8 folders (Box 392)
            - S-Z, 5 folders (Box 393)
          - Housing, A-Z (Box 393)
        - State, Secretary of
          - General
            - A-L, 2 folders (Box 393)
            - M-Z (Box 394)
          - Material file (Box 394)
          - Michigan Historical Commission (Box 394)
        - Treasury
          - Allison Green (Box 394)
          - General
            - A-N, 5 folders (Box 394)
            - O-Z, 3 folders (Box 395)
        - Urban Affairs (Box 395)
        - Volunteers in Michigan (Box 395)
      - Federal Subjects 1978
        - A-E (Box 395)
        - F-S (Box 396)
        - S-Z (Box 397)
      - Legislative: General 1978
        - A-L, 4 folders (Box 397)
        - M-Z, 8 folders (Box 398)
    - 1979
      - General Subjects 1979
        - A-C (Box 399)
        - C-I (Box 400)
        - J-L (Box 401)
        - L-P (Box 402)
        - P (Box 403)
        - Q-R (Box 404)
        - S-V (Box 405)
        - W-Z (Box 406)
        - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 406)
        - Habitual Letter Writers, 3 folders (Box 406)
      - Departments and Commissions 1979
        - Management and Budget (formerly Administration)
          - Director's File (Gerald H. Miller) (Box 407)
          - General
            - A-M (Box 407)
            - N-Z (Box 408)
          - Aging Commission, 3 folders (Box 408)
          - Crime Victims Compensation (Box 408)
          - Criminal Justice (Box 408)
          - Health and Medical Affairs, A-Z, 3 folders (Box 409)
          - Retirement, 5 folders (Box 409)
          - State Administrative Board (Box 409)
          - Veterans' Trust Fund, 2 folders (Box 409)
        - Agriculture
          - Director's File (Dean Pridgeon) (Box 409)
          - General, A-Z, 3 folders (Box 410)
        - Attorney General
          - Frank J. Kelley (Box 410)
          - General, A-Z (Box 410)
        - Civil Rights
          - Director's File (Ruth Rasmussen) (Box 410)
          - General, A-Z (Box 410)
        - Civil Service
          - Director's File (Richard A. Ross) (Box 410)
          - General, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 410)
        - Commerce
          - Director's File (William F. McLaughlin) (Box 410)
          - General
            - A-C (Box 410)
            - D-Z (Box 411)
          - Consumers Council, A-Z (Box 411)
          - Economic Expansion
            - A-Z, 5 folders (Box 411)
            - Foreign Letters (Box 412)
          - Energy
            - A-S, 10 folders (Box 412)
            - T-Z (Box 413)
          - Insurance Commission, A-Z, 5 folders (Box 413)
          - Liquor Control Commission
            - A-Z (Box 413)
            - Material file (Box 413)
          - Public Service Commission
            - Chairperson's File (Daniel J. Demlow) (Box 413)
            - General
              - A-M, 5 folders (Box 413)
              - N-Z, 4 folders (Box 414)
        - Corrections
          - Director's File (Perry M. Johnson) (Box 414)
          - General
            - A-P, 7 folders (Box 414)
            - O-Z, 2 folders (Box 415)
          - Inmates
            - A-J, 7 folders (Box 415)
            - K-Z, 8 folders (Box 416)
        - Education
          - Superintendent's File (John W. Porter) (Box 417)
          - General
            - A-H, 5 folders (Box 417)
            - I-Z, 8 folders (Box 418)
        - Highways
          - Director's File (John P. Woodford) (Box 418)
          - General
            - A (Box 418)
            - B-M, 8 folders (Box 419)
            - N-Z, 5 folders (Box 420)
        - Labor
          - Director's File (C. Patrick Babcock) (Box 420)
          - General
            - A-D, 4 folders (Box 420)
            - E-Z, 9 folders (Box 421)
          - Michigan Economic Opportunity Office (Grants) (Box 421)
          - Michigan Employment Securities Commission
            - Director's File (S. Martin Taylor) (Box 422)
            - General, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 422)
        - Licensing and Regulations
          - Director's File (William S. Ballenger, III) (Box 422)
          - General, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 422)
        - Lottery, State
          - Commissioner's File (Gus Harrison) (Box 422)
          - A-Z (Box 423)
        - Mental Health
          - Director's File (Frank M. Ochberg) (Box 423)
          - General
            - A-R, 3 folders (Box 423)
            - S-Z, 2 folders (Box 424)
        - Military Affairs
          - Director's File (John A. Johnston) (Box 424)
          - General, A-Z (Box 424)
        - Natural Resources
          - Director's File (Howard A. Tanner) (Box 424)
          - General
            - A-E, 4 folders (Box 424)
            - F-R, 7 folders (Box 425)
            - S-Z, 3 folders (Box 426)
        - Police, State
          - Director's File (Gerald L. Hough) (Box 426)
          - General
            - A-L, 4 folders (Box 426)
            - M-Z, 5 folders (Box 427)
        - Public Health
          - Director's File (Maurice S. Reizen) (Box 427)
          - General
            - A-H, 4 folders (Box 427)
            - I-Z, 7 folders (Box 428)
        - Social Services
          - Director's File (John T. Dempsey) (Box 428)
          - General
            - A-Bri, 3 folders (Box 428)
            - Bro-Hol, 7 folders (Box 429)
            - Hom-Q, 7 folders (Box 430)
            - R-Z, 9 folders (Box 431)
          - Housing (Material/A-Z), 7 folders (Box 432)
        - State, Secretary of (Michigan Historical Commission) (Box 432)
        - Treasury
          - Allison Green (Box 432)
          - General
            - A-N, 4 folders (Box 432)
            - O-Z, 3 folders (Box 433)
        - Urban Affairs (General A-Z) (Box 433)
        - Volunteers in Michigan (Box 433)
      - Federal Subjects 1979
        - A-J, 10 folders (Box 433)
        - K-Z, 19 folders (Box 434)
      - Legislative: General, 1979
        - A-B (Box 434)
        - C-Z, 6 folders (Box 435)
    - 1980
      - General Subjects 1980
        - A-C (Box 436)
        - C-I (Box 437)
        - I-L (Box 438)
        - L-P (Box 439)
        - P (Box 440)
        - P (Box 441)
        - Q-R (Box 442)
        - R-S (Box 443)
        - S-T (Box 444)
        - U-V (Box 445)
        - Miscellaneous
          - A-M, 2 folders (Box 445)
          - M-Z (Box 446)
        - Habitual
          - A-V, 4 folders (Box 446)
          - W-Z (Box 446)
      - Departments and Commission 1980
        - Agriculture
          - Director's File (Dean Pridgeon/Material)
            - General, A-Z (Box 447)
        - Attorney General (Frank J. Kelley/Material/A-Z) (Box 447)
        - Civil Rights (General A-Z) (Box 447)
        - Civil Service (A-Z/Material) (Box 447)
        - Commerce
          - Director's File (William F. McLaughlin) (Box 448)
          - General, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 448)